Finding Aid for the Julian Goodman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- NBC Corporate – Reports
  - Reports
    - Network Television Executives – Dissertation by Susan H. Johnston – title page and table of contents, 1986 (Box 96, Folder 17.)
    - “Days of Penury, Days of Affluence, Undated (Box 96, Folder 18.)
  - Reports - Financial
    - Salary Plans/Analysis, 1958 – 1977 (Box 97, Folder 1.)
    - Report/Fact Book, 1959 – 1969 (Box 97, Folder 2.)
    - Play Investments, 1966 – 1970 (Box 97, Folder 3.)
    - Program development and costs, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 4.)
    - Report/Fact Book, 1969 – 1973 (Box 97, Folder 5.)
    - Executives expenses, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 6.)
    - Executive employment – salaries, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 7.)
    - September 1972 (Box 97, Folder 8.)
    - the Economy, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 9.)
    - Television Network Sales Information, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 10.)
    - Television Network Sales Information – the DuPont Company, 1973 (Box 97, Folder 11.)
    - “Advertising in a Recession”, October 1973 (Box 97, Folder 12.)
    - Competitive Analysis – Networks, 1973; 1978 (Box 97, Folder 13.)
    - Budget and 5 Year Projections, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 14.)
    - Budget and 5 Year Projections – TV Network, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 15.)
    - Budget and 5 Year Projections – Radio, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 16.)
    - Business Plan Briefing Package, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 17.)
    - Pre-tax profit, 1974 (Box 97, Folder 18.)
    - January 1974 (Box 97, Folder 19.)
    - April 1974 (Box 97, Folder 20.)
    - Television Network Sales, 1975 (Box 97, Folder 21.)
  - Reports – Financial
    - (Company Private), October 1975 (Box 98, Folder 1.)
    - (Sections 1 -2 ), May 1976 (Box 98, Folder 2.)
    - (Sections 3 – 4), May 1976 (Box 98, Folder 3.)
    - (Sections 5 – 7), May 1976 (Box 98, Folder 4.)
    - Payroll Analysis, May 1976 – 1977 (Box 98, Folder 5.)
    - September 1976 (Box 98, Folder 6.)
    - Consolidated Statements for 1974 – 1975, 1976 (Box 98, Folder 7.)
    - 1978, Consolidated Statements for 1976 – 1977 (Box 98, Folder 8.)
    - Management Incentive Compensation Plan, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 9.)
    - “NBC Television Network Business Plan”, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 10.)
    - Salary Actions, August 1978 (Box 98, Folder 11.)
    - September 1978 (Box 98, Folder 12.)
    - (Sections 1 -2), October 1978 (Box 98, Folder 13.)
    - (Sections 3 – 5), October 1978 (Box 98, Folder 14.)
    - (Sections 6 -8 ), October 1978 (Box 98, Folder 15.)
  - Reports – Financial
    - (Sections 1 – 3), December 1978 (Box 99, Folder 1.)
    - (Sections 4 – 8), December 1978 (Box 99, Folder 2.)
    - Business Review, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 3.)
    - Business Review – TV Stations, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 4.)
    - Business Review – TV Network, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 5.)
    - Business Review – Radio, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 6.)
    - Business Review – News, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 7.)
    - Statements – Profits, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 8.)
    - January 1979 (Box 99, Folder 9.)
    - February 1979 (Box 99, Folder 10.)
    - Business and Long Range Plans, 1979 (Box 99, Folder 11.)
    - “NBC Cable News Channel Business Plan”, July 1985 (Box 99, Folder 12.)
- NBC Corporate – Subject Files
  - Subject Files
    - ABC and I.T. and T Merger, 1965 (Box 100, Folder 1.)
    - ABC and I.T.T. Merger (Box 100, Folder 2.)
    - AFL Football and Heidi (Box 100, Folder 3.)
    - Aiken, Senator George D. (Box 100, Folder 4.)
    - AIM “Accuracy in Media”, May 1976 – March 1977 (Box 100, Folder 5.)
    - AIM “Accuracy in Media”, March – April 1977 (Box 100, Folder 6.)
    - AIM “Accuracy in Media” –AIM “Accuracy in Media, 1977 (Box 100, Folder 7.)
    - American Irish Historical Society (Box 100, Folder 8.)
    - Applicants, 1967 (Box 100, Folder 9.)
    - Astron Enterprises Corporation/ O’Connell, Jack (Box 100, Folder 10.)
    - Baker, Russell (Box 100, Folder 11.)
    - Baseball – L.A. Dodgers, 1966 (Box 100, Folder 12.)
    - BBC (Box 100, Folder 13.)
    - Bicentennial Planning, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 14.)
    - Bicentennial Planning, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 15.)
    - Bicentennial Planning – Yearbook, 1974 (Box 100, Folder 16.)
    - Broadcasting Career Recruitment Film, 1965 (Box 100, Folder 17.)
    - Broadcast Standards, 1967-1968 (Box 100, Folder 18.)
    - Burger, Chief Justice Warren E. (Box 100, Folder 19.)
    - Bush, George H.W., 1974 (Box 100, Folder 20.)
    - Butz, Earl (Secretary of Agriculture) (Box 100, Folder 21.)
    - Cable Television – articles by Thomas Whiteside and others (Box 100, Folder 22.)
    - Cable Television –address by Clifford M. Kirtland, 1972 (Box 100, Folder 23.)
  - Subject Files
    - Carter, Amon, Jr. – 1919-1981- invitation; obituary (Box 101, Folder 1.)
    - CBS, 1968 (Box 101, Folder 2.)
    - CBS, 1969 (Box 101, Folder 3.)
    - CBS, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 4.)
    - CBS – “Meet the Press”, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 5.)
    - CBS, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 6.)
    - CBS, March 18 – July 13, 1971 (Box 101, Folder 7.)
    - CBS, June 30 – October 1971 (Box 101, Folder 8.)
    - CBS, 1972 (Box 101, Folder 9.)
    - CBS, 1974 (Box 101, Folder 10.)
    - CBS, 1975-1976 (Box 101, Folder 11.)
    - CBS, 1977 (Box 101, Folder 12.)
    - CBS, 1978-1987 (Box 101, Folder 13.)
    - Chandler, Otis (Box 101, Folder 14.)
    - Cigarette advertising, 1970 (Box 101, Folder 15.)
    - Cigarette smoking – study, May 1971 (Box 101, Folder 16.)
    - Color television, 1965 – 1968 (Box 101, Folder 17.)
  - Subject Files
    - Color television, 1969-1970 (Box 102, Folder 1.)
    - Consultants – Booz, Allen, and Hamilton, 1976; 1980 (Box 102, Folder 2.)
    - Consultants – Lippincott and Margulies – NBC Logo, 1974-75 (Box 102, Folder 3.)
    - Consultants – Lippincott and Margulies – NBC Logo, 1976 (Box 102, Folder 4.)
    - Consultants – Lippincott and Margulies (Box 102, Folder 5.)
    - Coronation, 1953 (Box 102, Folder 6.)
    - Correspondents’ Year End Tour, January 1974 (Box 102, Folder 7.)
    - Daley, Richard (Mayor of Chicago), 1968 (Box 102, Folder 8.)
    - DeGaulle, Charles – Funeral, 1970 (Box 102, Folder 9.)
    - Disney, Walt – productions (Box 102, Folder 10.)
    - Dougherty, Russell, General – USAF, 1977-78 (Box 102, Folder 11.)
    - Dulles, John Foster – Funeral, May 27, 1959 (Box 102, Folder 12.)
    - Elections and other news coverage, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 13.)
    - Emergency Power/blackouts, 1966 (Box 102, Folder 14.)
    - Emmy Awards, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 15.)
    - Energy Crisis, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 16.)
    - Enterprises – domestic, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 17.)
    - Enterprises – international, 1966-67 (Box 102, Folder 18.)
    - Equal Time Provision (Section 315), 1971 (Box 102, Folder 19.)
    - Equal Time Provision (Section 315), 1974 (Box 102, Folder 20.)
    - Equal Time Provision (Section 315), 1976 (Box 102, Folder 21.)
    - European Broadcasting Union, 1971 (Box 102, Folder 22.)
    - FBI –J.Edgar Hoover, 1959- 1971 (Box 102, Folder 23.)
    - First Amendment- “History of the Ogden Standard-Examiner”, 1972 (Box 102, Folder 24.)
    - First Amendment – Freedom of the Press (Box 102, Folder 25.)
    - First Amendment – Freedom of the Press, January – April 1976 (Box 102, Folder 26.)
  - Subject Files
    - First Amendment – Freedom of the Press, May – August 1976 (Box 103, Folder 1.)
    - First Amendment – Freedom of the Press (Box 103, Folder 2.)
    - First Amendment – Freedom of the Press (Box 103, Folder 3.)
    - First Amendment – Freedom of the Press (Box 103, Folder 4.)
    - Forbes, Malcolm – Transatlantic Balloon Flight, 1974; “the Atlantic Project” (Box 103, Folder 5.)
    - Forbes, Malcolm – Transatlantic Balloon Flight, 1974; “the Atlantic Project” (Box 103, Folder 6.)
    - Forbes, Malcolm – Transatlantic Balloon Flight, 1974; “the Atlantic Project” (Box 103, Folder 7.)
    - Ford Foundation, 1966 (Box 103, Folder 8.)
    - Foreign Memos (non NBC), 1966 (Box 103, Folder 9.)
    - Frye, Robert E. – ABC News (Box 103, Folder 10.)
    - Goldsmith, Dr. Alfred N. (Box 103, Folder 11.)
    - Goldwater, Barry (Senator) (Box 103, Folder 12.)
    - Governors, 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 13.)
    - Gulf Oil Corporation – Sponsorship, 1960 (Box 103, Folder 14.)
    - Gulf Oil Corporation, Sponsorship -1961 (Box 103, Folder 15.)
    - Gulf Oil Corporation – William K. Whiteford, Chairman, 1964 (Box 103, Folder 16.)
    - Gulf Oil Corporation- Sponsorship, 1971-1972 (Box 103, Folder 17.)
    - Gulf Oil Corporation – Sponsorship, 1974 – 1977 (Box 103, Folder 18.)
  - Subject Files
    - “Heidi” Bowl, November 17, 1968 (see also AFL subject file) (Box 104, Folder 1.)
    - Hertz Corporation, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 2.)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H. – Discover America 1966; Operation VIP 1968 (Box 104, Folder 3.)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1969 (Box 104, Folder 4.)
    - Humphrey, Hubert H., 1977 (Box 104, Folder 5.)
    - Iran, Imperial Embassy/Ambassador Ardeshir Zahedi (Box 104, Folder 6.)
    - Iran, Imperial Embassy/Ambassador Ardeshir Zahedi (Box 104, Folder 7.)
    - Iran, Imperial Embassy/ Ambassador Ardeshir Zahedi (Box 104, Folder 8.)
    - Kennedy, Robert F. – Requiem Mass Invitation June 8, 1968 –telegram; notes from RFK speaking off the record April (Box 104, Folder 9.)
    - Landers, Ann (Eppie) (Box 104, Folder 10.)
    - Law Department, 1974 (Box 104, Folder 11.)
    - Law Department, 1975 (Box 104, Folder 12.)
    - Lewis, Jerry (Box 104, Folder 13.)
    - Lower, Elmer/Television News\ (Box 104, Folder 14.)
    - MacDonald Hearings on Broadcast License Renewal, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 15.)
    - MacDonald Hearings – “Topless Radio”, 1973 (Box 104, Folder 16.)
    - McKinney, Robert M.- photocopy of typescript “The Bolshoi Ballet’s Last Tour” (Box 104, Folder 17.)
    - Mexico, 1972 (Box 104, Folder 18.)
    - Mexico – “A Salute to Televisa”, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 19.)
    - Mexico – “A Salute to Televisa”, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 20.)
    - Motion Pictures (Box 104, Folder 21.)
    - Murrow, Edward R. (Box 104, Folder 22.)
  - Subject Files
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, January – February 1976 (Box 105, Folder 1.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, February – March 1976 (Box 105, Folder 2.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, March – June 3, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 3.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary- Correspondence, June 4 - 15, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 4.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, June 16 – 22, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 5.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, June 23 -24, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 6.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, June 25, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 7.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, June 28 – 29, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 8.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, June 30 – July 6, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 9.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Correspondence, July 7 – November 12, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 10.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Book – Golden Years of Broadcasting (Box 105, Folder 11.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Book – Golden Years of Broadcasting (Box 105, Folder 12.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Book – Golden Years of Broadcasting (Box 105, Folder 13.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – Dinner Program, June 22, 1976 (Box 105, Folder 14.)
    - NBC 50th Anniversary – New Logo (Box 105, Folder 15.)
    - NBC Forum, 1977 (Box 105, Folder 16.)
    - NBC History (Box 105, Folder 17.)
  - Subject Files
    - NBC 60th Anniversary – Issue of Television/Radio Age, May 1986 (Box 106, Folder 1.)
    - NBC 60th Anniversary – Inside NBC – 60 years (Box 106, Folder 2.)
    - Netcom – World Satellite Television – Post Retirement, 1982-1983 (Box 106, Folder 3.)
    - New York Times – A. D. Sulzberger (Box 106, Folder 4.)
    - News Program Service – 19th Anniversary, 1979 (Box 106, Folder 5.)
    - News Staff Memos, 1965 (Box 106, Folder 6.)
    - News Staff – Domestic (Box 106, Folder 7.)
    - NIS (News and Information Service) – Report “The First Results” (Box 106, Folder 8.)
    - NIS (News and Information Service) – “Wheel of Programs”, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 9.)
    - NIS (News and Information Service), January-July 1976 (Box 106, Folder 10.)
    - NIS (News and Information Service), September 24 – October 28, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 11.)
    - NIS (News and Information Service), November 1-12, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 12.)
    - NIS (News and Information Service), November 12- November 24, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 13.)
    - NIS( News and Information Service), November 29 –December 17, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 14.)
    - NIS (News and Information Service), January – May 1977 (Box 106, Folder 15.)
    - Olympics (Box 106, Folder 16.)
    - Operations and Engineering, 1974 (Box 106, Folder 17.)
    - Palmer, Arnold (Box 106, Folder 18.)
    - Pastore, Senator John O., 1969 (Box 106, Folder 19.)
    - Pensions/AIM, 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 20.)
    - Pensions/AIM, 1975 (Box 106, Folder 21.)
    - Pensions, 1976 (Box 106, Folder 22.)
    - People’s Republic of China, 1977-1979 (Box 106, Folder 23.)
    - Policy, 1966-1967 (Box 106, Folder 24.)
  - Subject Files
    - Presidential Coverage – State of the Union, 1957-1970 (Box 107, Folder 1.)
    - Presidents – American Heritage Special Issue: “The Presidency”, August 1964 (Box 107, Folder 2.)
    - Presidents – Campaigns in AP World, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 3.)
    - Presidents – “The Presidency and the Press” by D.P. Moynihan, 1971 (Box 107, Folder 4.)
    - Presidents – Carter, Jimmy (as democratic candidate), 1976 (Box 107, Folder 5.)
    - Presidents – Carter, Jimmy – Television Coverage, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 6.)
    - Presidents – Carter, Jimmy, 1977-78 (Box 107, Folder 7.)
    - Presidents – Carter, Jimmy – Television Coverage, 1978 (Box 107, Folder 8.)
    - Presidents – Carter, Jimmy – Cabinet (Box 107, Folder 9.)
    - Presidents – Carter, Jimmy – Invitations (Box 107, Folder 10.)
    - Presidents – Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 107, Folder 11.)
    - Presidents – Eisenhower, Dwight D. (Box 107, Folder 12.)
    - Presidents – Ford, Gerald R. (Box 107, Folder 13.)
    - Presidents – Ford, Gerald R. in Broadcasting Magazine, December 23, 1974 (Box 107, Folder 14.)
    - Presidents – Ford, Gerald R. – White House visit, March 1975 (Box 107, Folder 15.)
    - Presidents – Ford, Gerald R. – Cabinet, 1975 (Box 107, Folder 16.)
    - Presidents – Ford, Gerald R., 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 17.)
    - Presidents – Ford, Gerald R., 1976 (Box 107, Folder 18.)
    - Presidents – Ford, Gerald R., 1976 (Box 107, Folder 19.)
    - Presidents – Ford, Gerald R., 1977-1978 (Box 107, Folder 20.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1963 (Box 107, Folder 21.)
  - Subject Files
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964 (Box 108, Folder 1.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1964 (August - December) (Box 108, Folder 2.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1965 (January – May) (Box 108, Folder 3.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1965 (June – October) (Box 108, Folder 4.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1966 (February - April) (Box 108, Folder 5.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1966 (May – July) (Box 108, Folder 6.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1966 (September – December) (Box 108, Folder 7.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1967 (April – December) (Box 108, Folder 8.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1967 (January – March) (Box 108, Folder 9.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B. – Confidential reports by Ray Scherer, 1968 (Box 108, Folder 10.)
    - Presidents – Johnson, Lyndon B., 1968 (January – April); 1985 (Box 108, Folder 11.)
    - Presidents – Kennedy, John F., 1963 (Box 108, Folder 12.)
    - Presidents – Kennedy, John F. – Assassination – “Oswald Affair” (Box 108, Folder 13.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – NBC Coverage, 1953-1974 (Box 108, Folder 14.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M., 1966 (Box 108, Folder 15.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M., 1968 (Box 108, Folder 16.)
  - Subject Files
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M., 1968-1969 (Box 109, Folder 1.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. -- Agnew, Spiro (vice president), 1969 (Box 109, Folder 2.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Television Network Coverage, 1969-1971 (Box 109, Folder 3.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M., 1970-1971 (Box 109, Folder 4.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Today Show interview transcript with Barbara Walters, March 11, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 5.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Television Network Coverage, 1972-1973 (Box 109, Folder 6.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Television Network Coverage, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 7.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – “The White House vs. Television News” by Dick Adler in the Los Angeles Times, May 13, 1974 (Box 109, Folder 8.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M., 1974 (Box 109, Folder 9.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M., 1975 (Box 109, Folder 10.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Julian Goodman Remembrance Letter, 1976 (Box 109, Folder 11.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Cabinet, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 12.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Cabinet, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 13.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Cabinet, 1973-1974 (Box 109, Folder 14.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Cabinet – Colson, Charles (Box 109, Folder 15.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Cabinet – Colson, Charles (Box 109, Folder 16.)
    - Presidents – Nixon, Richard M. – Cabinet – Colson, Charles (Box 109, Folder 17.)
    - Presidents – Reagan, Ronald (Box 109, Folder 18.)
    - Presidential Campaign Debates – Report, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 19.)
    - Presidential Elections and Television, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 20.)
    - The Press, 1967; Bill Barrett; Bernie Harrison (Box 109, Folder 21.)
    - The Press/Publicity, 1970 (Box 109, Folder 22.)
    - The Press, 1971 (Box 109, Folder 23.)
    - The Press – Martin, Bob, 1972 (Box 109, Folder 24.)
  - Subject Files
    - The Press, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 1.)
    - The Press, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 2.)
    - The Press, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 3.)
    - The Press, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 4.)
    - The Press, 1976 (Box 110, Folder 5.)
    - The Press – Broadcasting Magazine – Sol Taishoff, 1976-1982 (Box 110, Folder 6.)
    - The Press – Broadcasting Magazine -- NBC Executives, 1981 (Box 110, Folder 7.)
    - The Press – Broadcasting Magazine – Lawrence Taishoff (Box 110, Folder 8.)
    - The Press – Broadcasting Magazine, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 9.)
    - The Press – Louis D. Boccardi, 1985 (Box 110, Folder 10.)
    - Press/Broadcast News Councils (Box 110, Folder 11.)
    - Press Releases, 1982 (Box 110, Folder 12.)
    - Public Affairs – Tanglewood – Boston Symphony Orchestra, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 13.)
    - Public Relations – Proposal, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 14.)
    - Public Service Announcements – The White House -- October, November 1974 (Box 110, Folder 15.)
    - Public Service Announcements – The White House, November – December 1974 (Box 110, Folder 16.)
    - Public Service Announcements, January – September; 1974 (Box 110, Folder 17.)
    - Radio and Television Correspondents Association, 1959-1977 (Box 110, Folder 18.)
    - Radio Television News Directors Association, 1966 – 1969 (Box 110, Folder 19.)
    - Radio Television News Directors Association (RTNDA) – Retirement article by Elmer Lower, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 20.)
    - Retirement Letters, 1974 (Box 110, Folder 21.)
    - Rockefeller Center Properties (Box 110, Folder 22.)
    - Rockefeller, John D.,III and the third sector, 1978 (Box 110, Folder 23.)
  - Subject Files
    - Satellite Communications, 1970 (Box 111, Folder 1.)
    - Satellite Communications – “A Communications Satellite System for the United States – Why Not Now” by Leonard H. Marks and related materials, November 1970 (Box 111, Folder 2.)
    - Satellite Communications, January – July 1971 (Box 111, Folder 3.)
    - Satellite Communications – Report – “Television Program Distribution Service”, February 16, 1971 (Box 111, Folder 4.)
    - Satellite Communications, 1973-1978 (Box 111, Folder 5.)
    - Schmidt, Gert Hans Werner, 1980 (Box 111, Folder 6.)
    - Selecta Vision (Box 111, Folder 7.)
    - Sinatra, Frank (Box 111, Folder 8.)
    - Smiley, Donald B. – Macy Chairman (Box 111, Folder 9.)
    - Space Flights, 1962 (Box 111, Folder 10.)
    - Sullivan, Joseph T. P. – Obituaries, 1989 (Box 111, Folder 11.)
    - Telecommunication for the Deaf (Box 111, Folder 12.)
    - Teletext, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 13.)
    - Television – The Early Years, 1950s (Box 111, Folder 14.)
    - Television – The Early Years, 1950s (Box 111, Folder 15.)
    - Television – Television Quarterly – Winter, 1979-1980 (Box 111, Folder 16.)
    - Television Networks (Box 111, Folder 17.)
    - Television Networks – Talent (Box 111, Folder 18.)
    - Television News as Entertainment (Box 111, Folder 19.)
    - Television Columnist – Terry Turner (Box 111, Folder 20.)
    - UNESCO – Draft Declaration, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 21.)
    - U.S. Congress Directory, 1953 (Box 111, Folder 22.)
  - Subject Files
    - U.S.S.R., May – June 1973 (Box 112, Folder 1.)
    - U.S.S.R., 1974 (Box 112, Folder 2.)
    - Violence on Television, 1970-71 (Box 112, Folder 3.)
    - Violence on Television, 1974 (Box 112, Folder 4.)
    - Violence on Television, 1975-1977 (Box 112, Folder 5.)
    - War Department (Box 112, Folder 6.)
    - West, Mae, 1937 (Box 112, Folder 7.)
    - Women and Employment at NBC, 1972-1973 (Box 112, Folder 8.)
    - Zanuck, Darryl (Box 112, Folder 9.)
- NBC Corporate – U.S. Government
  - Central Intelligence Agency, 1977-1978 (Box 113, Folder 1.)
  - U. S. Government - Congress
    - Correspondence, 1969 (January-May) (Box 113, Folder 2.)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (May-August) (Box 113, Folder 3.)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (September – October) (Box 113, Folder 4.)
    - Correspondence, 1969 (October – December) (Box 113, Folder 5.)
    - Report – Deceptive Programming Practices, 1969 (Box 113, Folder 6.)
    - House of Representatives Correspondence, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 7.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1970 (1) (Box 113, Folder 8.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1970 (2) (Box 113, Folder 9.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1970 (3) (Box 113, Folder 10.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1970 (4) (Box 113, Folder 11.)
    - Senate Correspondence – Re: Pastore, 1970 (Box 113, Folder 12.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 13.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1971 (Box 113, Folder 14.)
  - U.S. Government – Congress
    - Senate Correspondence, 1971 (February-March) (Box 114, Folder 1.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1971 (March-April) (Box 114, Folder 2.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1971 (April –May) (Box 114, Folder 3.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1971; Sam Ervin – Re: Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters (Box 114, Folder 4.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1971; Sam Ervin – Re: Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters (Box 114, Folder 5.)
    - Senate Correspondence, 1971; Sam Ervin – Re: Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters (Box 114, Folder 6.)
    - House of Representatives Correspondence, 1971 (Box 114, Folder 7.)
    - “Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters” – Letters, 1971 (March 19 – 24) (Box 114, Folder 8.)
    - “Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters” – Letters, 1971 (March 25 – 31) (Box 114, Folder 9.)
  - U.S. Government – Congress
    - “Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters” – Letters, 1971 (April 1-6) (Box 115, Folder 1.)
    - “Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters” – Letters, 1971 (April 7-12) (Box 115, Folder 2.)
    - “Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters” – Letters, 1971 (April 13-27) (Box 115, Folder 3.)
    - “Constitutional Rights of Broadcasters” – Letters, 1971 (May 6-20) (Box 115, Folder 4.)
    - Commentary on NBC, 1972-1973 (Box 115, Folder 5.)
    - Supreme Court – Brief of NBC as Amicus Curiae, 1973 (Box 115, Folder 6.)